>> Brian Holt: 我现在想让你去
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I want you now to go to
SearchParams.js， >> Brian Holt: And
SearchParams.js,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
我们会把所有按钮都用我们的理论
we're gonna make all the buttons
use our ThemeContext.
因此，在此处，我希望您从 "./ThemeContext" 中导入 ThemeContext 。
So at the top here, I want you to import
ThemeContext from './ThemeContext'.
>> Brian Holt: 我们还会从 React 中获取另一个叫做 useContext的挂钩。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And we're also gonna get
another hook from React called useContext.
布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 好的，然后在宠物下面
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and
then up here underneath pets,
我们会说康斯特主题
we're gonna say const Theme.
记住这也有一个 setTheme 。
And keep in mind that this also
comes with a setTheme as well.
但我们不会用这个 setTheme ，所以我就不去抓它了。
But we're not gonna use the setTheme,
so I'm just not gonna grab it.
因此， const [theme] = useContext >> Brian Holt: (ThemeContext)。
So const [theme] = useContext
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: (ThemeContext).
>> Brian Holt: 因此， ThemeContext 可能是什么。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So again,
ThemeContext could be anything.
这可能是对象，不一定是数组或
This could be an object, it doesn't
necessarily have to be an array or
一个钩子什么的
a hook or anything like that.
他们只是方便地使用对方
They're just convenient to
use with each other, but
他们比那更有弹性
they are more flexible than that.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，我有这个主题，可供使用，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now, I have this theme,
which is available to use,
所以我要按我的按钮
so I'm gonna go down to my button.
>> Brian Holt: 此处，在此 " 提交 " 按钮中，我将表示样式 = 和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Here, at this Submit
button, I'm gonna say style = and
就像一个专业的直插式 CSS 一样
just do some inline CSS
like a professional.
开个玩笑别这么做
[LAUGH] Just kidding, don't do this.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，通常，您希望这是颜色: 空白或
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So typically, you would
expect this to be color: blank or
那样的东西对吧
something like that, right?
React 使其更容易一些，您可以将其保留为对象。
React makes it a little bit easier,
that you can just keep it an object.
所以我只能说颜色: 主题。
So I'm just gonna say
color: theme like that.
现在注意的是两条大的，但是
Now notice there are two curly
braces next to each other, but
发现它们的颜色不同，因为这是一个物体，对吧 ?
notice they're colored differently,
that's because this is an object, right?
这是 JX 的 JavaScript 表达式。
And this is the JavaScript
expression from JSX thing.
所以彼此相邻的两条小牙套都没有什么特别的
So it's not that two curly braces next
to each other have any sort of special
在 JSX中的含义。
meaning in JSX.
这就是看起来的样子
That just happens to be how that looks.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，现在，如果你过去看看我们的项目。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so, now if you
go over and look at our project.
抱歉，您不需要颜色，需要背景色。
Sorry, you don't want color,
you want background color.
我是说通知还有效吧
I mean notice it still worked, right?
这个颜色是蓝色的，但这不是我想要的。
The color of this is blue, but
that's not what I intended.
我想让它成为背景色。
I intended this to be backgroundColor.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 然后你就会去，现在是深蓝色的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And there you go,
now it's dark blue.
>> Brian Holt: 我们来谈谈，我的意思是，很明显，这是很多种仪式
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Let's talk about, I mean,
obviously this was a lot of ritual to
从中获益很少，但让我们来谈谈为什么这很重要。
get very little benefit out of it, but
let's talk about why this was important.
我在上面有 App.js ，对，在这个主题提供程序中。
I have App.js here on the top, right,
which I've wrapped in this theme provider.
然后在 SearchParams 里面，我没有把任何东西都传给 SearchParams。
And then inside of SearchParams, notice I
haven't passed anything into SearchParams.
通常你得做点什么
Typically, you would have
had to do something like
themeColor = ，对吗 ?
themeColor = , right?
你也得做同样的事情然后把它传递给每个人
And you'd have to do the same thing with
details and pass it into every individual
从主题中读取的应用程序的内容，对吗 ?
piece of your application that
read from the theme, right?
那是负担对吧
That's burdensome, right?
你会得到某种程度的负担而不是有用的，对吧 ?
You get to a certain point where it gets
more burdensome than it's useful, right?
所以这就是这些背景非常有用的地方。
So that's where these
contexts are super useful.
而不是把它明确地传递给 SearchParams
That instead of having to pass
this explicitly into SearchParams,
现在我可以进入 SearchParams了
now I can go into SearchParams.
SearchParams ，我可以从上下文中读出来。
SearchParams, and
I can read off of the context.
现在我可以在我和
Now I could have infinite
layers between me and
提供给你还是有用的对吧
the provider and it still works, right?
正好是有提供者的直系人
It just happens to be that it's the
immediate parent that has a provider but
可能有 17 层
there could be 17 layers.
实际上，如果你看一下你的资源管理器里的路由器代码，
And actually, if you look at the reach
router code inside of your Explorer,
让我们看看现在的情况， " 检查元件" 。
let's actually just look at that
right now, Inspect Element.
它们在任何地方都使用上下文。
React, they use context everywhere.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，您可以看到引用的上下文提供程序，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So you can see there
are context provider for ref,
上下文使用者。
context consumer.
他们在这里有一堆东西上下文消费者
They have a bunch of stuff in here,
context consumer,
上下文使用者，上下文提供程序。
context consumer, context provider.
有一群消费者和提供者。
There's a bunch of layers of consumers and
providers.
这一切都与背景有关。
That all has to do with context.
>> Brian Holt: 这真的很容易和 useContext 一起使用，这是一个钩子，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So it's really easy to use
with useContext, which is a hook, right?
>> Brian Holt: 在我们开始讨论如何处理类之前，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Before we move
on to how to deal with classes,
有人对你目前的情况有什么疑问吗
does anyone have any questions
about what you've seen so far?
>> 扬声器 2: 要使用 useContext ，上下文提供程序必须是父代吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So to use the useContext,
the context provider has to be a parent?
>> Brian Holt: 对。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yep.